<resources>

    <!--String Resource file for Privacy Fragment-->
    <string name="privacy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="updated">Last Updated: August 18, 2015</string>
    <string name="aboutHeading">About Flavors:</string>
    <string name="aboutValue">Flavors allows food enthusiasts all over the world to plan, host and attend food events at convenient locations including nearby restaurants.  We make it easy for everyone to discover food events, and to share information about the food events they are attending with the people they know through Facebook and other applications.</string>
    <string name="policyHeading">Privacy Policy:</string>
    <string name="policyValue">The term \'Flavors\', \'us\' or \'we\' refers to the owner of the application. The term \'you\' or \'user\' or ‘host’ refers to the users of the application. We take the privacy of your Personal Data and other information very seriously. We will not share any of the personal information with third party providers for marketing, research or for any other reasons.  Please read this privacy policy carefully as it contains important information.   Your use of any information or materials on this application is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any information available through this android application meet your specific requirements.This application contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the code, design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.</string>
    <string name="infoHeading">Information we collect from you:</string>
    <string name="infoValue">When you login to our application, we collect personal profile details from your Facebook account. Profile details include Facebook id, name, email and profile photos. The application also collects optional information such as food interests, date of birth and mobile number. We use these details if you are attending any events, so that the organizer can contact you through email.  We also use these information if you are organizing any events, so that the users can know details regarding the host. We collect the information mainly to enable whole operation of the application and to personalize your experience on the Service.We also collect the user current location using the google location and play services. This information is used just for tracking distance and will not be stored anywhere. Event Organizer may use the details about the users who have joined the event. Flavors will not be responsible in the event of misuse of personal details by event organizer.We may use your Personal Data for internal business purposes including without limitation to help us improve the content and functionality of the Services, to better understand our users, to improve the Services, to protect against, identify or address wrongdoing.</string>
    <string name="changesHeading">Changes to This Privacy Policy:</string>
    <string name="changesValue">The Policy and the application might change from time to time. As a result, at times it may be necessary for us to make changes to this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time (collectively, "Modifications"). Modifications to this Privacy Policy will be posted in this screen with a change to the "Last Updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Services following the effectiveness of any Modifications to this Privacy Policy constitutes acceptance of those Modifications. If any Modification to this Privacy Policy is not acceptable to you, please stop accessing, browsing and otherwise using the Services.</string>
    <string name="storageHeading">Storage and Security:</string>
    <string name="storageValue">We store personal information parse cloud storage. Even though parse takes reasonable steps to protect the personal data. Since, no application is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from the Services may not be secure. We will not be responsible if any information is leaked inadvertently. </string>
    <string name="tncHeading">Other Terms and Conditions:</string>
    <string name="tncValue">Your access to and use of the Services is subject to the Terms of Service.Please look in Terms of Service page for details</string>
    <string name="modHeading">Modifications to or Deletion of Personal Information:</string>
    <string name="modValue">If for any reason you wish to modify or delete your Personal Information, you may contact us to delete the information from backend servers.  Upon your request on Flavors administrators will remove your Personal Information from the application data within 10 working days.</string>
    <string name="contactHeading">Storage and Security:</string>
    <string name="contactValue">Please also feel free to contact us if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information practices. You may contact us at +1 315 751 4826 / +1 860 805 9344 or by email at <a href="#">reachflavors@gmail.com</a> </string>
    <string name="disputeHeading">Dispute Resolution:</string>
    <string name="disputeValue">If you have a complaint about Flavors privacy policy you should write to us at Flavors, 427 and Half Columbus Avenue, Syracuse, 13210 or by email to <a href="#">reachflavors@gmail.com</a>. We will take reasonable steps to work with you to attempt to resolve your complaint.</string>

</resources>
