<resources>

    <!--String Resource file for Terms Fragment-->
    <string name="terms"><u>Terms of Use:</u></string>
    <string name="update">Updated on: 18 August 2015</string>
    <string name="head">\'You\' and \'user\' refer to you, as a user of this android application. A \'user\' is someone who accesses, browses, login or in any way uses the android application. \'We\', \'us\', and \'Flavors\' refer to Flavors. By installing and using the Flavors Mobile Application, you agree to our use of your personal information and terms of use as stated in the below sections of this screen. The application will use camera, gps and other functionality for better user experiences.</string>
    <string name="appHeading">App Use:</string>
    <string name="appValue">Flavors grants you the right to use the App only for personal use. You must comply with all applicable local laws and third party terms of agreement when using the app. The Flavors committee will not be responsible for any copyright content published by the event hosts. In case the event hosts have published any copyright material including photos, description etc.  Please do inform us and we will remove the content from the application as soon as possible.</string>
    <string name="acceptHeading">1.Acceptance of Terms</string>
    <string name="acceptValue">By installing and logging in the Flavors application, you acknowledge that you have read and understood the Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy terms. Also you agree to be bound by them and to comply with all applicable laws and regulations regarding your conduct on Flavors. If you do not agree, please close the application and uninstall from your android mobile device. The Flavors will periodically update the terms of service / use in the mobile application. The updated date will be displayed on the top of the screen. It is the responsibility of the user to check periodically the terms and conditions. Google will not be responsible for any support services for this app or the content.</string>
    <string name="eligibilityHeading">2.Eligibility</string>
    <string name="eligibilityValue">You should be above 18 years to access this Flavors application or the legal age of majority where you reside if that jurisdiction has an older age of majority, to login to the application. In any case if you age is less than 18 years.</string>
    <string name="limHeading">3.Limitations of Liability </string>
    <string name="limValue">We will not be responsible for any losses occurred for hosts who organize the event. We will not be responsible for any damages caused to the mobile while using the application or after installing the application. We will not be liable under any circumstances or under any legal theory. We will not be responsible for any direct, indirect, accidental, incidental, special, consequential losses loss / damage. The application might crash, stop or not function sometimes. The services might be interruptible, timely, error free or might not fit the requirements.  The content provided by hosts might be copyrighted content sometimes, in such an event, please drop an email to <a href="#">reachflavors@gmail.com</a> to remove the content. We will remove content as soon as possible.<br/>In any case the hosts upload any copyright content, objectionable content or images which don’t relate, the Flavors committee has full responsibility to remove the images, delete the event. The Flavors disclaim liability for any (i) INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, EXEMPLARY, RELIANCE, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, (ii) LOSS OF PROFITS, (iii) BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, (iv) REPUTATIONAL HARM, OR (v) LOSS OF INFORMATION OR DATA. The maximum liability in case of event shall be 5$. Flavors will not assure THE QUALITY, SAFETY OR LEGALITY OF ANY CONTENT OR EVENTS CONDUCTED, EVENTS ATTENDED, THROUGH THE SERVICES, OR THE SERVICES THEMSELVES (OR ANY PART THEREOF), WILL MEET YOUR EXPECTATIONS. All the Events are organized by the hosts and Flavors will not involve, monitor or check the authenticity of the events. We will not be liable for the quality of the food served and the ingredients information. The event menu information is completely provided by the event hosts and we will not have any control over that.</string>
    <string name="termsHeading">4.General Terms</string>
    <string name="termsValue">Participation in the home event or restaurant event is completely voluntary we will not be responsible for any consequences resulting from that. In-Order to login to application, the users should possess a Facebook account to login. The user credentials are not stored in our system and is authenticated by Facebook. The payments are directly collected by event hosts and it is not linked or there is no commission paid to us. The reservation cancellation by guests are to be informed directly to hosts. We will not act as a mediator in cancelling the participation. Thus the participation is completely voluntary and based on your risk, we will not be able to provide any liability or refunds whatsoever.</string>
    <string name="restHeading">5.Restrictions</string>
    <string name="restValue">While creating an event, any copyright images will be removed us without any intimation. Please use the original images / content for the application. Any attempt to inject dummy data or large dataset will result in violation of TOS and will have serious consequences. Also you agree not to Threaten, stalk, harm, or harass others, or promote bigotry or discrimination, Solicit personal information from minors, or submit or transmit pornography; Record, process, or take information about other users; You also agree that you will not remove, damage or destroy other user information.</string>
    <string name="thirdHeading">6.Third Parties</string>
    <string name="thirdValue">The Site may include links to other websites or applications (each, a \'Third Party Site\'). We do not control or endorse any Third Party Site. You agree that we are not responsible for the availability or contents of such Third Party Sites. Your use of Third Party Sites is at your own risk.</string>
    <string name="terminationHeading">7.Termination</string>
    <string name="terminationValue">We might, in sole discretion, may terminate your accounts and the right to use the application, and remove and discard any and all of your content within the Services, at any time for any reason or no reason, including, without limitation, for lack of use, if we believe that you have violated or acted inconsistently with the spirit of this TOS. We reserve the right to modify, update, or discontinue the application at our sole discretion, at any time, for any or no reason, and without notice or liability.</string>
    <string name="linksHeading">8.Links</string>
    <string name="linksValue">We might provide links to other resources or websites like Facebook.</string>
    <string name="tradeHeading">9.Trademark Information</string>
    <string name="tradeValue">The Logo’s, application names and some of the images are trademark of Flavors. Other company, product, and service names used in connection with the Services may be trademarks or service marks owned by third parties.</string>
    <string name="violateHeading">10.Violations / Support / More Information / Questions</string>
    <string name="violateValue">For any queries or questions, please contact us at <a href="#">reachflavors@gmail.com</a>. We will consider the concerns and provide response as soon as possible.</string>

</resources>
